hello what are you doing back again
okay so these are repelling and they're
approximately
uh well that's saying eight but if we go
to where the measure is it's just
unknown
so you can see that there from top to
bottom
is nine centimeters
or 90 millimeters
it's approximately there so i'll just
wrap that on top more just holiday just
for the
for the sake of being being afraid
but what we've found is that we've we
can actually
get it to go to attraction and that's
quite unusual
so the the measurement of this is
uh from from there
up to here is um
50 54
54 centimeters so overall from the base
is approximately 60.
a bit over okay but from where this
magnet's
leaving off that washer
would be just on 60 centimeters
so this is how brilliant
this is just look at this
so it does come apart
but and the most amazing part is it goes
together
so it goes together
and the with a small amount of vibration
on it fires it apart alrighty
now why would you want to be able to use
this
what would be the benefit and what we
found
is that we've got similar devices or
smaller devices just a simple tube
with a funnel this has been blown for us
by a local
glassblower and i'm using some of these
that just pop in there so you can see it
and that in turn water is flowing in
through here
and down and out through the nozzle a
few parts for that
silver silver one the small one yep
that's it it's just the one this this
particular one
has the nozzle and this is configured to
attack
and this is what this is basically doing
it's spinning
the water past the magnets and
what is it it's causing a form of poly
water
or polymer water water that becomes
separated
it's no longer remaining in a constant
flow
each particle or droplet of water is a
separate individual
it's wetter it's nicer to taste
it's got rid of a lot of the colloidal
minerals that are normally
stacked inside
what we call water where did they go
yeah that's a good question where did
they go
um once they fit within the spiral that
i showed you before with dr walter
russell's stuff
it spins and becomes a new charge
and those elements become available
later stage
as energy or crystalline structures
within your body that's what's giving
you
energy and the electrical frequencies
throughout your body
okay so that's where those things go you
don't see them
they become opaque or clear
and taste beautiful
they aren't negative oils some are
negative
some are even positive the number of
them
some as we showed you before go from 0
1 2 3 4 positive
sit at a point of balance and then go
down
4 three two one zero
negative and that's probably the most
amazing today's performance a
nine spiral
and all of the elements that we've been
able to find doctor walter rockwell
us subatomic particles particles well
before hydrogen
which according to mandalos periodic
tables begin
at hydrogen so he showed there being
about 26 elements well and truly alive
and well
back in 1921 uh that was sub-atomic
particles
and he also showed the atomic range of
elements
some of which he even said were unknown
so any wonder was still finding it
um so within this unit i'll just show
you quickly
uh the magnets that we were playing with
before
and there they are there so this
particular one's got three
what we'd normally put in in this unit
are four just that i wanted to
experiment a little bit
and there they are there and
they just pop back inside
when they're being nice to me i've just
got to get rid of that one put the
smaller one on
so they actually have four inside
i've just got a couple there they're a
little bit big um
you can just see the different sizes so
practicable
they fit nicely in there and then they
get done
and this particular your tap fitting
fits
directly onto that and your hose fitting
next
straight onto that so these units were
actually
retailing out at the moment um probably
in the vicinity of about 150 dollars
so these treats were water magnetically
the other units we have are nearly two
thousand dollars
i'd like you to just pass me one of
those
what we've done is another the bigger
units
what we've done is that we've sorry yeah
these
are different types of fittings so you
can put it directly on the end of the
hose
and then just spray the water out from
that end
okay so here we have an absolutely
amazing
device so please if you've got any
problems with your heart
do not buy one of those um if you've got
a pacemaker things like this these are
four neodymiums there's nine of them
within it
and they will knock you over or restart
your heart i
believe
we've made it so that they're adjustable
when they come back in and get serviced
uh we just pull them apart re-energize
the cell by removing all of the minerals
that have been attracted to the
particles
or back to the the center of the unit so
um
this is this is what it looks like just
so this magnets there on that long
tube yep so this
these in actual fact get put
into the center of these so um
that that's that's how they look when
you when you're buying them
and they're quite quite unique um
the only the only problem is like with
most magnets
uh that particular unit we're retailing
out
just on two and a half thousand dollars
in australia and these get rid of most
of the
materials that that
are high calcium height
contaminants that are you know
flocculated particle so these
all come apart and sit within themselves
quite nicely you can see they're in
repulsion
all of them some are in different fields
we won't tell you what the field
structures are
because we want to supply those two
and these get sealed in the unit you
don't actually get to play
with this part of it but only because of
the strength
and the alignments are just so important
so that's we believe we can
even disassociate up to
uh heavy metals and possibly even
radioactive particles
i went to japan and met up with
the wonderful man dr emoto whilst i was
in japan and
when i left i gave him one of these
units to hopefully continue to do
further experimentation
in helping to clean up the waters in
japan um
so this when you look at our site which
is where the creation.com
these are the fun things that you'll get
to see that we're working with
weather creation is rather unusual in
that we
believe we are the cause of rain as well
so have a look at the size
we're playing with magnets in such an
unusual way
but we're also doing a lot of research
and some of what we're trying to do is
bring
dr walter russell's technology back into
the life
and uh show you guys since uh
you're a lot smarter than me i'm only
playing
we'd like to be doing some serious stuff
the weather creation is
certainly serious the water filters
are certainly serious as uh
the water conditioner for your garden
and things like that so absolutely
fantastic so thank you very much
the world issue oh all right yeah look i
just had
had to put in that we're uh we're
helping clean up
the waters in bangladesh
in fact believe that it doesn't really
matter where you are
in the world you're affected by
magnetism
so if you happen to be inside planet
earth
here here's planet earth coming out of
its
uh magnetic field uh in its out in its
outer shells and it's ionosphere and
stratosphere
the structure of the magnetics
are that the earth can i believe
spin onto different poles
and these are the poles that i'm
referring to so they can
change their angle and probably have
done in the last ten thousand years or
ten thousand years ago
places like antarctica were most likely
other areas of tropical vegetation or
whatever so
they were just tilted onto different
poles so if you like if we just did a
lucky dip as to which way it went
uh it could have ended up anyway so
these are the structures
that it's likely to move on so
this is just a dodecahedron and a simple
or if you like the simple soccer ball so
that's what it looks like
inside some of the paintings from the
elders or the old
masters showed
even the last supper having this type of
device
surrounded it in the back of it so
rather unique
so thank you really appreciate it and
let's uh show you the website
weathercreation.com
and you come on back now you're here